I don't know what this video is because
I have like ten topics in my head
running around and I can't seem to pick
just one of them so instead I'm kind of
gonna just talk about the angsty anxiety
the need to get done in the world
but not being able to do it myself
knowing a vision of how we can do it
together not be able to communicate it
but more than that because that's my
everyday all day anxiety that's
underlying that I've come to peace with
but I had a conversation on Monday was
somebody who very much identifies as a
at least my opinion no you know clearly
it's like the shadow that's more of what
they identify with in the light I
identify mostly with light but I love
and embrace my shadow as well and I do
truly think that everybody is exactly
who they are supposed to be on this
planet because it keeps proving itself
to me and yet sitting with this
conversation that we had it's probably
one of the most powerful single
conversations that I have had it is up
there in teaching me stuff with two of
my big conflicts that I've had in the
last couple of years which were much
more emotionally triggering this one
wasn't it's just it's there's levels of
learning there and I'm gonna be
processing but it's also kind of left me
with a feeling of anxiety a feeling of
like what do we do with people who are
shadow more shadow and do we do anything
how do we help them do what they're here
to do and so I've also been I'm just
going to talk about all of the things
but getting out of them because I'm not
gonna go in time you come to deeply
these four questions that I'm obsessed
with right now which are like the Who am
I who are my people what's my purpose
what do I need
and in those questions there's so much
depth because they're never answered but
in answering them is the internal reward
that helps you continue with the rest
there's just and so they heard their own
video keep trying to a video on all four
together and it ends up being half an
hour maybe it needs to be half an hour
then this like opposite of a Dunbar
number having enough people in the meta
community to be able to find your people
so that there is space for everyone
everyone's shadow everyone's light and
then being part of the new Omega
conversation yesterday I'm talking about
new games to play and the lingo and
needed to be easy with the lingo they
think is easy isn't a lingo I think is
easy and you know being able to create
avatars and characters to play the game
and there's something about that that
I'm both like yes there's beauty because
of this shadow side that you can pretend
to be somebody else and at the same time
with these questions I'm sitting with
part of the payoff and Who am I is that
the more you live in your authenticity
the more you can find your community
that truly accepts you for you and the
more you're playing in an avatar the
safer that is and the more you're like
willing to play the game but at the same
time you're not actually getting it
makes the internal reward of being seen
for who you are and so and then my other
Omega conversation that is long-standing
starts is today in less than half an
hour and so I'm just sitting with all of
these things and I propose some topics
for the Omega group which for all
binaries except for one which is like
the sphere of mists you know and one of
the people was like well those sound
like they all fit under the category of
balance
Mikey yes that is a ID that's what we
need and this balance like why I do hold
the opposite of a lot of binaries I can
hold opposing views within myself and
truly hold them and yet I want to choose
right I want to be like no we need the
avatar or we get to do authenticity and
yet I can see that the game is truly
giving people
what they feel safe with that some
people need to have an avatar I need to
be able to play into something try on
different roles to be able to find who
they are and feel safe and they might
never get that peace and internal reward
that comes with being who you truly are
and being accepted for it and finding
your people and at the same time they
get a taste of people seeing them and
liking them for who they are even if
they are trying on you know maybe some
of these shadow characters if there are
shadow characters in the game we're
creating and so yeah that is I don't
know why doing a video on this except
that I wanted to be on one of them so
much that I came on it game but a video
on all of them which is very much how my
mind and life work just sitting with it
and dealing with the emotions and then
not smoking pot none of those things out
and like everything is exactly how it
should be but I also really want to get
the done like I want yeah I don't
want it like I want it done without me
because I don't want to happen like I
can't physically do the work and yet I
don't want to I don't want to miss out
on conversations that are the thing
that's gonna spark the idea that is game
be and you can't be part of all the
conversations I'm sitting with the fear
of Miss you know to this balancing
authenticity and played an avatar and
said you have a large group you've done
bar number and these four questions and
how they are the key to everything
oh it's fun it is fun to be me so I just
wanted to share a little slice of my
chaotic internal dialogue and why maybe
it's hard for me to pick one topic and
then I will pick I will be talking about
probably all of those topics in their
own individual video